

BUILDING FOR THE WEB

Victor Isaac

in https://linkedin.com/in/victor-isaac



https://twitter.com/IsaacVictron



https://victhereum.github.io

Phone

+2348124182627

Fmail

tamsvictorisaac@outlook.com

Location

Lagos, Nigeria

About me

I'm an enthusiastic and passionate programmer with over 2 years of experience using various programming languages and web frameworks to build and maintain websites and web apps. Experience in designing and developing sites from concept to rollout. grasp of various programming languages like C#, Python, JavaScript, and framework options like ASP.NETCore, Django, etc. including development platforms and security requirements. I am fluent in English and is able to undertake with utmost perfection jobs I am privileged to have.

Experience

Freelance Web Developer, KCLStores, FeronAuto, Agro-Matic, Sureseis, StBarnanbasFoams)

2019 - Present | Port Harcourt,

Nigeria

- * I have worked on a few web projects contracted to me by startups and businesses
- * Discussed site and app requirements with clients to produce actionable development plans and budgets.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, Python
- Designed, implemented, and monitored web pages, plugins, and functionality for continuous improvement.

Web Developer, Agro-Matic/ Web Dev PH

2021 - 2022 | Port Harcourt, Nigeria

- * Successfully worked with a team in creating, designing, and launching www.agromaticstaking.farm, a crypto staking platform for the Agro-Matic cryptocurrency
- * Contributed to team success by completing jobs quickly and accurately.
- * Developed strong cooperative relationships with coworkers and managers.
- Sought out ways to go above and beyond job requirements.

Education

Interlink Polytechnic

2019 - 2022 | Ijebu-Jesa, Nigeria

Computer Science, HND

Built a facial recognition attendance system for my final year project

Port-Harcourt Polytechnic

Computer Engineering, ND

2016 - 2019 | Port Harcourt, Nigeria

- Graduated with a 3.3/4.0 Upper Credit
- Built a real-time computer for my ND projectz
- · Assisted lecturers and lab facilitators in building embedded systems

Skills Languages

Blockchains | Ethereum | Solidity | Django Web Framework | .NET Framework | C# | Python | Web Development | Embedded System | Computer Science | Web3 | MVC

English (Intermediate)